

Kajendrani Koy

CONTENT ASSOCIATE



ABOUT ME

Dogmatic and fun-loving content writer with experience in a variety of industries, including education, healthcare, and travel. Skilled in writing compelling narratives that capture the reader's attention and drive conversions. Key achievement: Generated unique content through the craft of narrative storytelling.



CONTACT

(+91)9875335294
rajendraniroy2014@gmail.com
28/5, Gariahat Road (South) Dhakuria
Kolkata - 700031.



EDUCATION

 N.S.H.M Knowledge Campus-Group Of Institutions

Bachelor in Pharmaceutical Engineering

2013 - 2017

 St. John's Diocesan Girls' High School

Graduated with Science stream

1998 - 2013



WORK EXPERIENCE

Content Associate
Chegg India Pvt. Ltd, 2021 - Now

PMT Executive In Marketing Department KonTest Chemicals Limited, Kolkata, 2018 - 2021

Q.C. Executive (Jr. Chemist)

KonTest Chemicals Limited, Hyderabad, 03/2018 - 07/2018



SKILLS | EXTRAS

- Good SEO Knowledge
- Adaptability
- · Delivering Quality Content
- Organizational Skills
- Ability To Produce the Best Result In Pressure Situation
- Communication Skill
- · Ability To Meet Deadlines



LANGUAGES

Bengali

English

Hindi